In an era in which the nations of
the world were waging a fierce war
of information just out of sight,
two countries were at odds with
each other: Ostania, in the east,
and Westalis, in the west.
In order to keep an eye on the actions of
a leading figure in Ostania's government
who was planning a war,
Westalis set Operation Strix in motion.
The one tasked with this operation
is the skilled agent, Twilight.
The mission given to the master of
disguise with a hundred faces was...
to start a family.
The father, Loid Forger, is a psychiatrist.
His true identity: a spy.
Code name: Twilight.
The mother, Yor Forger, is a civil
servant who works at city hall.
Her true identity: an assassin.
Code name: Thorn Princess.
The daughter, Anya Forger.
Her true identity: a telepath
who can read people's minds.
The dog, Bond Forger.
His true identity: a canine seer
who can see the future.
They created this pretend
family for their own benefit,
and their mission continues as they all
hide their identities from each other.
Part of the Family
Bond, we're going for a walk.
Borf.
Borf!
You wanna go, too?
Anya's not going.
Bhork!
Anya is busy right now.
Difficulty level max.
Origami?
Apparently, it's very popular
at school right now.
She's concentrating really hard.
If she's not coming today,
I guess we'll do some training
rather than go on a walk.
All right. We're off.
Have a nice time, Loid, Bond.
Go!
That's right.
Go after your target's arms or
legs to render them powerless.
Don't go after vital points that
could cause fatal wounds, though.
Then I won't be able to get
any intel out of them.
You bastard! Did you forget how
much I've taken care of you?!
Hey!
Once you bite your target,
absolutely do not let go!
It's risky for you, and biting your target
more makes a fatal wound more likely.
Maybe you're too nice, and barking
and biting don't really suit you.
You know...
Why am I playing the suspect, anyway?!
Again, I'm an informant, and—
I need to train him. I have no other choice.
How am I your only option?!
Well?! Tell me! Tell me
in 500 characters or less!
Things are getting really fishy right now,
so I need to prepare for the worst.
That literally answered nothing!
All right. That's enough suppression
and protection training.
Let's do some training on order
sorting and locating explosives.
It's really hard to learn.
Wait, am I supposed to participate?
Am I supposed to be the bomber?
What's wrong? I guess you've
used up your concentration.
Project Apple is where they did experiments
to make intelligent army dogs, right?
He probably had to go through a lot of
training and doesn't want to do it anymore.
I see...
You can't even do this? What a stupid mutt.
I guess the project is a failure.
These mutts will probably be disposed of.
To the doggo here, training and
combat are basically like playing.
At least try to act like you're having fun.
You're always lacking in that department.
Take him on a walk or something
for a change of pace.
So yeah, I'm going home.
Hey!
Guess we can go for a walk.
Borf!
Wow, you've made so many!
Those little stars are so cute.
Tsk, tsk, tsk. They are no ordinary stars.
"Anya Holger! I present
you with this Stella!"
Ye!
Don't eat stuff off the ground.
My ice cream! I barely got to eat it!
What a loser! From now on,
your name's gonna be Icesplatio.
No!
Double-scoop ice cream!
It's not fair that you get
more allowance than us.
Borf!
Ah, so you protected this
child's food. Good boy!
It was definitely worth taking you in!
Hey!
Whoa! What the heck's wrong with this bear?!
Is he after my ice cream?
Bond, stop! What's wrong with you?!
My ice cream! I barely got to taste it!
I'm sorry, lad! I'll buy you another one!
Three scoops! Three scoops!
No fair.
Seriously.
It's not like you to try to
get at someone else's food.
What's gotten into you? Are you hungry?
Hurgh!
I'm so sorry! Are you all right?!
Someone call an ambulance!
You're acting really weird today!
What the heck is this beast?!
I'm so sorry!
I apologize for my dog's rudeness!
You clearly haven't trained him properly!
Biting an unknown civilian is unacceptable.
I'll have to thoroughly retrain you.
You're amazing, Bond! You saved the future!
Borf!
Borf...
This is strange.
I've done basic socialization and
obedience training with him already,
and he's never been a reckless dog.
Just like with Anya, I guess I still
have a lot to learn about him.
Oh, ew! A pigeon just pooped on me!
Precognition
What he thinks
will happen
That's enough! Now we're
gonna get rid of you!
Is he sick?
Maybe I should take him to the vet.
Daisy!
Ma'am, you mustn't! Stay back!
But Daisy's still inside!
No! Daisy!
What's the matter?
He's really on edge today.
Hey! No!
Borf!
That's...
Someone call the fire department!
The fire's spreading faster than expected!
A fire?
Was he reacting to the smell?
Is there anyone inside?
Not to worry. Everyone made it out.
There have been a lot of these lately.
I've heard rumors that it's actually arson.
Where's that fire truck?!
Daisy! Daisy!
Wha—
You dummy, don't! There's no one inside!
Don't you go in there, too!
Wait. Maybe he smells someone...
Bond! Bond!
Bond!
That's hot! What the hell are you doing?!
A puppy... Does it live here?
You're ridiculous, you know that?
We need to get out of here, though.
Can you run?
Keep as low to the ground as you can!
Our way out...
He's clearly scared of the fire.
We can't force our way through.
This is bad. What should we do?
Most of the bottom floor's
been engulfed in flames.
The only way out is the outdoor
staircase north of here.
There's a chance it might
fall apart, but...
Bond, come!
Hey, what are you doing?!
This is no time to play around!
Y-You saved me.
Your nose works even at times
like this? You're really amazing.
This means the outdoor
staircase is a no-go.
Which means we'll have to
force our way through the smoke.
I'll be fine, but Bond's running out of air.
A plastic bag...
Okay, we'll take this and... take in
some of the clean air down here...
And we've got ourselves
a makeshift oxygen tank.
We'll get through the places
where we can't breathe with this.
Borforf.
Let's put her in here so we can carry her.
Don't get lost. Make sure you follow me!
Borf!
Let's go!
Hey! You made it out safe!
Apparently this little one
was left in apartment 407.
Hey! This is Ms. Bennett's puppy!
I guess she didn't get out in time.
And he went in to save her?
What an impressive dog!
Bond! You're on fire! Fire!
Wait one sec! I'll bring a bucket of water!
You're so skinny!
Is that... how you look when you're wet?
I always have Yor bathe him, so this
is the first time I've seen this... It's...
No, you mustn't, Twilight.
I am a cool-headed spy.
I cannot let my emotions show.
The fire's out. Good for you.
What's the matter?
Hey!
Sir, can you look after that puppy?
S-Sure...
Hey! Wait a second, Bond!
Holy crap! Just look at that epic blaze!
Daisy!
Ma'am, you mustn't! Stay back!
But Daisy's still inside!
I could never give this shit up!
Whoa! What the hell is
that skinny, wet thing?!
Ow! Let go of me, you dumb mutt!
He managed to bite another civilian!
Why, you—
Oil and ignition tools?
Don't disrespect a human, you piece of shit!
You knew he was the arsonist?
This is the same oil that the police
said was used in the other arson cases.
We'll just report him to the police
and let them deal with him.
I'm surprised you noticed.
Was his scent at the scene?
Or was the arsonist letting
off his unique stress scent?
Well, either way, well done.
Oh, thank goodness, Daisy!
I'm so glad you're safe!
I don't know what I would've
done if I'd lost you.
Oh, Daisy! I'm so sorry!
This serious-looking guy and
this huge, skinny dog saved her.
They truly deserve an award.
I'll go find them.
Let's go. It wouldn't be good if
either of us ended up in the paper.
And the bestest boy gets
a year's worth of meat.
You did well. I'm really impressed.
But...
I told you to bite their arm, not their leg!
Don't push yourself too hard.
There's someone waiting back home
who would be sad if you died.
I'm sorry, too.
Putting you to work can take a back seat.
First and foremost, you need to fully
realize that you're one of the Forgers.
Got it?
Are you hurt at all?
You probably inhaled a lot of smoke.
Let's have you checked out just in case.
What are you doing?
Hey, stop that!
Don't get ahead of yourself.
This is just because I can't afford to let any
member of the Forger family be eliminated.
I don't have a mission tomorrow, so why don't
we all go to a dog park? It's been a while.
You're the only one who didn't get to enjoy
the vacation since you stayed behind, anyway.
Why does your barking
change when you're wet?
The bright crimson that
appears right before my eyes
Stretches approximately 40,000 kilometers
Our wounds that inch closer behind us
Make us wander even more
when we're already lost
The unseeable, scentless, unmistakable future
Stabbed me in the back!
So...
Let me stay by your side tonight
Just for tonight, I'm going to be serious
Come closer to me
Even the future we prayed for
Has a different path
My dear
Our malice for each other
Might just get to us
Or maybe not
I did it!
Is it a knife?
Huh? I-It's a penguin...
Origami is rather difficult.
Oh, I know. How about something like this?
Ta-da!
Ooh!
Oh, dear. I guess I cut
them up a bit too much.
We're back.
Welcome home.
B-Bond! You've shrunk
down to almost nothing!
Oh, my. What happened?
You wouldn't believe it.
Someone accidentally sprayed
water on him on our way home.
Oh, I see.
His voice is different, too?!
It's all right, Miss Anya.
This is what happens to
Bond when he gets wet.
Once he dries, he'll be back
to his usual fluffy self.
It's not like I can tell them that he rescued
a puppy from a fire and caught an arsonist.
Papa and Bond worked
extra hard on this walk!
Bond, just a moment. I'll dry you right off.
Thanks, Yor.
Papa!
Papa! Bond! I present you
both with these Stellas!
What's this? Are you playing
with pretend Stellas?
It's the "Worked Super
Hard on Your Walk" award.
Wow! Bond, Loid, congratulations!
This is fine and all, but could
you get some real Stellas?
Shock!
All right. Let's get dinner going.
I'll help.
Anya wants to eat Papa's Hamburg steak!